

Adama Simon James

Frontend Developer

Summary

Creative Front-End Developer offering 1.9 years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse organizations. Skilled in designing, and developing multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies. Aspiring to combine broad background with strong technical skills to excel as a Front-End Developer.

Do I sound like a good fit for your team?

CONTACT

- simontoviaadama@gmail.com
- ******* +2348056595398
- im simon-adama-69a1711a4
- Toviarock1

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

BOI-UAT-TECH HUB

Feb 2022 - Dec 2022

Frontend Developer

FREELANCE

Apr 2021 - Sep 2021

- -Implemented enhancements that improved web functionality and responsiveness.
- -Managed front-end development of client side.
- -Worked closely with programmers to meet client project requirements, goals, and desired functionality.
- -Coding of UI/UX designs into digital applications.
- Frontend Developer Intern

SIDEHUSTLE

Jan 2021 - Apr 2021

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

NextjsReactjsReduxTypescriptJavascriptJQueryCSSHTMLTailwindcssAntdGit Version ControlLinuxBootstrap

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science - BS
UNIVERSITY OF AFRICA TORU, ORUA